when working with Word documents there
may be occasions where you need to
insert information in a table format
there are two ways of doing this within
word and the first way is quite
straightforward so if I go up to the
insert tab and I selected insert and
then on the table I can't select it
insert table I can then create a table
with a number and columns and rows that
I would require so as long as I knew how
many columns and rows I needed I could
insert that so I'll just select that as
an example and as you can see it has
inserted five columns and six rows the
problem there is I still need to
populate at the table with the
information so if I just undo that by
come on it said an alternative to that
is to actually import the information
and formatted as a table so I have the
information that I wish to enter into
the letter within this spreadsheet so
I'm just going to highlight the
information and use the command + C to
copy and then once I've copied I'd like
go back to the letter and place the
cursor where I want the information to
be entered and then I will use the
command + V so as you can see that
there's now Pierce that the information
into the letter but it's pretty much in
the same format as it was within the
spreadsheet so it doesn't look very
presentable there are a number of
pierced options and you will see it up
by the little clipboard at the bottom so
if I click on that I can keep the source
for Martin which is what it's doing at
the moment much destination table stale
pierced as a picture keep the text to
only keep source formatting and Link it
to excel so it would look the same but
it would be linked to the spreadsheet
much destination table style and link to
excel so that would put it into a table
within the document and then still link
it to excel so that meant that if any of
the data changed to a cinder they have
spreadsheet it would then update it in
the table within the letter so for this
example I'm just going to keep the text
only so I can demonstrate how you can
convert text to a table so I'll keep the
text and as you can see it doesn't look
very presentable and it's not very well
laid out so what I need to do is
need to highlight all of that
information and then go up to the insert
tab and select table and then convert
text to table so if I click on that now
it will ask me how many columns and rows
I want so it it actually knows there are
three columns Andy it was required
because it's already worked it out and
the column width is autor and it is
separated texts are tabs that basically
means that in between each of these
instances there is a tab symbol just to
show that if I click cancel and I go to
the horn menu and then select the show
hide button from the paragraph tools as
you can see there was a little tab icon
in between each of those that is what
it's allowing us to identify that it is
three columns and rows so if I just take
that back off there go back to the
insert table convert text to table three
columns it roars separate by tabs click
OK
and that has created a table with the
information included so from there when
I'm on the actual table design tab I can
then change the stale so I can apply
different table styles to the table I
can expand that so I can have a a wider
range of table styles so I'll just for
example select that one and again if I
want to make any more changes just
double click on the table you could add
shading borders tails different pen
colors and Lane with Sun various other
things like you may wish to experiment
with but that is how you can insert a
table from Excel into a document and
format it to make it look presentable